[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the multiplication sign, x, first used?", "correct_answer": "1631", "incorrect_answers": ["1731", "1531", "1831"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Walk the Line, a record executive says to Johny Cash, Whats with the black? You look like you are going to a funeral. What does Johny reply?", "correct_answer": "Maybe I Am", "incorrect_answers": ["Wishful thinking?", "Only my own", "He doesnt respond"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the cat hero described in Shirley Rousseau Murphys books?", "correct_answer": "Joe Grey", "incorrect_answers": ["Nermal", "Midnight Louie", "Pewter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the official Monopoly rules what happens if the bank runs out of money during the course of the game?", "correct_answer": "The game continues - additional money can be added", "incorrect_answers": ["Noone wins", "The game ends", "The game continues but players cannot get money from the bank anymore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2007 film 300 was losely based on the ancient Battle of Thermopylae. What does the name \u201cThermopylae\u201d mean translated from Greek?", "correct_answer": "Hot gateway", "incorrect_answers": ["Gateway of death", "Wide gateway", "Deadly gateway"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nixon received a higher percentage of the popular vote during his losing bid for the presidency than when he won in 1968.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two large vessels enter the right atrium of the human heart - the superior and inferior vena cava. They carry blood from the whole body and that is why this blood is dark red.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term blepharo derives from a Greek word and refers to which part of the body?", "correct_answer": "Eyelid", "incorrect_answers": ["Artery", "Larynx", "Lungs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ancient footsteps found in Tanzania prove that there were bipedal hominids as early as 3.8 million years ago.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the Latin word for pink?", "correct_answer": "Roseus", "incorrect_answers": ["Pinkueta", "Rosa", "Pinky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these is the motto of  the state of Missouri?", "correct_answer": "Salus populi suprema lex esta", "incorrect_answers": ["Semper ubi sub ubi", "Magnus inter opes inops", "Pares cum paribus facillime congregantur"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2004 action/adventure movie National Treasure, where do the Gates send Ian to seek the treasure, (which is on a wild goose chase), when the treasure cannot be found beneath the church?", "correct_answer": "The North Church", "incorrect_answers": ["Arlington Cemetery", "The Capitol", "Lincolns Bedroom"]}]